[
  {
      "title": "1:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "1 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 1,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "78082110-72c9-43cd-99bd-6fd8743622e9"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 2,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "ff6ca564-bd52-4ff5-995f-a97c33f2fb90"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 3,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b0aeedc1-8b8f-4624-acab-cf9f78b7666a"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 4,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "51cf3639-e89a-4a28-9509-cdd9da19dc24"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 5,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "584737e6-7fee-4f06-82af-cc75c9187e6b"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 6,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0785d81c-f54e-4428-8174-5a92a0cec127"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 7,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b9c21119-085f-494d-babf-b657692abe61"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 8,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "a506639c-397c-4af9-8292-9704d0815363"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 9,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "94903e66-ea70-4130-8a24-21de6f2f5d34"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 10,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "995b717a-d879-4b34-b2d6-5f3f6befa290"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 11,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "444e5e5e-46e7-404b-8d8c-d182094bf68d"
          },
          {
              "question": "1 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 12,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "2bfde55d-034d-48ee-9daf-4ce2d08a93e7"
          }
      ],
      "id": "3db74ce4-ab1d-44df-ac39-28b10a67578c"
  },
  {
      "title": "2:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "2 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 2,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "673f21cf-5890-4752-bbba-ef7ee69b2e24"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 4,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "e3611f32-9884-4c64-bd03-bfb5232d73a1"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 6,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "292e5e4c-d0c5-4cfb-9641-427dd1082033"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 8,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "14924f47-9b3d-4e73-88f9-c33d6c3e84f2"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 10,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "3b0bd63f-577a-4525-9d07-6fd8d4ccf4b0"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 12,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "a8585286-e3ac-4439-a7d0-ad2cc14c340b"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 14,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "732de789-e989-4b8a-86dd-6007692f3a76"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 16,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "cb2789c3-9b78-4ef2-98ba-8a3ac878835a"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 18,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0ad633e8-26e7-441f-8110-de6859b54e5a"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 20,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "3a132ea1-a274-49d4-8986-8592b355475e"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 22,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "1675bcd1-ea9a-44a5-9a4c-8a8e251cb30d"
          },
          {
              "question": "2 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 24,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "e65220b6-cd78-4a78-b35e-b76d14119b69"
          }
      ],
      "id": "3e9da8a0-422f-4166-b7e6-8c53f739dda4"
  },
  {
      "title": "3:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "3 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 3,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "4279eab0-c316-45df-90a0-6910b626d815"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 6,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "4d55b51e-5619-43ee-849a-a79d725731e7"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 9,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "2b421484-669e-41a1-a092-3b44073805ce"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 12,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "4ea61551-0e2f-458e-9359-4a81e165c7ac"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 15,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "d1f20e7f-e97f-4bd8-8e27-3120cb3ccb38"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 18,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "a3f753a9-57d1-430e-8bda-dedf17c50c74"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 21,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "c565e1a7-3aa2-445f-a8e8-8e622bca92cf"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 24,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "ad90210e-c5fd-47f4-82cc-acd46690b9c8"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 27,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "12bd496c-9eb9-42d9-b205-742fa2ca6093"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 30,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "cbb6ab39-e4fe-492c-bf3b-ffc88cbc7eef"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 33,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "5c9fea51-c7b7-428a-b1aa-c8b3ab343d5c"
          },
          {
              "question": "3 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 36,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "77ac568f-79ef-4d9e-8683-323b874ae593"
          }
      ],
      "id": "362d07bc-818f-495c-ac16-36b1449c7abe"
  },
  {
      "title": "4:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "4 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 4,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "828f54ea-658d-424f-8744-097a30a94bf9"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 8,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0fea5423-dfa2-42ba-822f-e2e0d34320cb"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 12,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "2b9638c9-8ffa-4473-9b60-c4b6385d89d7"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 16,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "e03a9801-abd8-4acb-90ec-dc9bce7d17ec"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 20,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "f82b68c6-f776-4a68-b1a0-dab16df05be3"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 24,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "04a9ae1e-e5a7-43bd-bbd8-2efc21b2f1e4"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 28,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "98cd018a-f157-480d-9fde-f0f8ba6c6bcf"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 32,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b8379984-e338-4529-b51f-9b16c929edef"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 36,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "4f53fc4f-5a87-496e-9c47-66bb82809e51"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 40,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "e614a2fb-ba85-4669-92ee-6ee02af99683"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 44,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "16fb850a-cae5-4fe8-9635-304cc5209554"
          },
          {
              "question": "4 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 48,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b68d5806-3cdd-4bb6-81db-33ae931d165b"
          }
      ],
      "id": "6b37a94b-1669-43b2-93ba-ad45bd0a1a73"
  },
  {
      "title": "5:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "5 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 5,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "3413bfba-4de5-41c4-8eea-d482979963e4"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 10,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "99b270dc-5d8a-4279-9c48-ac6fbc5cb718"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 15,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "9d9b785f-0bde-4fcc-86bc-26bcf32e333d"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 20,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "072a2571-78d8-4ea6-be2d-fe638ed837cc"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 25,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "c4d325f1-7f18-411a-828a-b51790322213"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 30,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "f08bbe22-da9d-4db6-bdb9-656c92174abd"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 35,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "3a01548a-de5e-4ae3-b676-3644c2fa6af4"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 40,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "64195ed9-7313-4340-b17f-689463713f02"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 45,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "cfa29083-04e3-407f-accc-48325c2afb8d"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 50,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "052c742a-e8b5-4226-99a4-2747357c43dd"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 55,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "19ae6f2c-8322-400b-b0d1-0da941014ce4"
          },
          {
              "question": "5 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 60,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "503d8617-2106-4394-b69b-24aa41dcff05"
          }
      ],
      "id": "cb4c5f52-cb27-4fa3-8092-be19b7b4c20b"
  },
  {
      "title": "6:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "6 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 6,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "6796e00f-3bd7-4db3-ade4-2d5b20da7400"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 12,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b186de18-b639-4353-b524-aa00e31310db"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 18,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "56641522-9bd4-4853-a9f1-51758f593e7d"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 24,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "e56cc020-c393-4fbe-91b7-ce776b5a2ab8"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 30,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0609f7b5-a4be-4011-ad7e-e6fbe79def40"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 36,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "137df6b0-2020-41b5-9bfa-3cd83e1bb0ba"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 42,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "d309329b-f7b2-42b2-a46c-b583d312e5f0"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 48,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "fef9d3e8-f787-42bb-ac6a-d8c69ee04801"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 54,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "f8336028-cbc2-4f9f-92a4-0b796db553ba"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 60,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "f0c24ad2-cd84-43eb-9680-0ce5ffcdbb44"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 66,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "7c55f5ff-c4ac-4b9c-84e6-05646ecc75bf"
          },
          {
              "question": "6 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 72,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "86c627de-052e-4424-84b5-6f67ee122f86"
          }
      ],
      "id": "6d6375f6-39c9-47be-a047-4d23ed8c7301"
  },
  {
      "title": "7:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "7 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 7,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0d2997e1-1019-43c2-bd14-a9d4113f4518"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 14,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "3ddad7d0-8612-43c9-9d16-aa29d37a8f7f"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 21,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "207eaf72-51f9-49fe-82c2-869d3bee38f5"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 28,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "7b0247f1-9faa-4ae3-8ecb-ac9c91d65baa"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 35,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "9a698b59-145f-4c0e-969b-f9cd926f7b89"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 42,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "72af09bf-a6c8-4d18-8436-a944d740832f"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 49,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "413db14b-497e-451c-84c8-88f871413b48"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 56,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "1caec34e-4cbc-4f4e-9f8f-526007cd8894"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 63,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "35c762ea-6f95-4bba-9508-36b62872a3b8"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 70,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "2bdffca2-79f2-4eff-96f9-ada9083d885e"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 77,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "5a3d08b9-ea54-429b-b806-84c27bfa220e"
          },
          {
              "question": "7 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 84,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "72e3d9df-34f4-44f9-93ba-ed478772f0e0"
          }
      ],
      "id": "448571eb-3049-479b-a67e-ff0193810167"
  },
  {
      "title": "8:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "8 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 8,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b823e7ff-4c0e-4482-8794-bf18f62ccdf1"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 16,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "a05ba8ee-60c1-49f6-aef9-549590e90130"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 24,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "c20af187-d93a-4ba3-af7a-1372e83fef4a"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 32,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "c9a47c45-9c6f-41d2-b861-53cde94b05a1"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 40,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "d25788f1-5476-4ac4-b28c-c7f67c318746"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 48,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "d8fdf73d-939f-44b9-a673-ded3f2debcd8"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 56,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "d9052d8a-5969-4be1-bc3e-6bc89b7d930e"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 64,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b087bc19-c0f6-454a-ab92-4c13dad20561"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 72,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "3a65ba84-b7c9-4a7c-b9d9-8aca49529cdb"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 80,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "25f77668-3454-4039-884a-02ddaa8674e9"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 88,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "7661f5fd-c05e-4de2-9004-b4057c9f30ab"
          },
          {
              "question": "8 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 96,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0690b452-24ae-422c-a4fd-46989a2ae0d6"
          }
      ],
      "id": "ad4e318e-7d4e-400d-bffd-a8cb8da24ca9"
  },
  {
      "title": "9:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "9 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 9,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "db109e55-de5a-4d48-bd76-cbd18356ec6a"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 18,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "6dc5175e-d83a-4837-a26e-69ab7c61bac3"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 27,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "9fda2082-04e1-4cf6-ace3-8c3736a24499"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 36,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "8e86ecc4-a5bf-46f9-8e56-a2ce5c3a18ae"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 45,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "cdd7b989-a089-4505-bc74-fc49b2765ed5"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 54,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "ac1b0c23-b9fb-4e30-b8e2-29f1abf1d6fd"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 63,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0beff9a0-928c-44aa-98fe-91a71ca6f17c"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 72,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "e5e7adfd-beb9-46da-af49-23599040db1d"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 81,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "20ab531a-ad43-42f8-bffd-2a7f2474e186"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 90,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0491e286-3cae-4faf-a26a-d69ab7ccd7e0"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 99,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "0f7ac72d-fc4a-4452-8979-5f60d3e686d6"
          },
          {
              "question": "9 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 108,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "595a35a5-bbda-4f10-bad9-01c718e05af3"
          }
      ],
      "id": "2aaeffaf-f4e4-4129-97c4-63e1f058f04f"
  },
  {
      "title": "10:ans gånger tabell",
      "cards": [
          {
              "question": "10 x 1 = ?",
              "answer": 10,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "78feb7d7-1fd9-4604-b88c-2b9e778806e8"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 2 = ?",
              "answer": 20,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "9f97901a-f326-4aaa-9cc8-87e26b0f32d8"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 3 = ?",
              "answer": 30,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "6cd28367-92a2-4255-be59-11fa994da853"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 4 = ?",
              "answer": 40,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "3a99a08d-0b01-4f68-a526-f49abb8a0a79"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 5 = ?",
              "answer": 50,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "14f4fd77-c0ca-401a-9665-e383111ec5ef"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 6 = ?",
              "answer": 60,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "815e6afa-c702-4697-b5b6-073a6ec96003"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 7 = ?",
              "answer": 70,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "b5ff9b0e-e4c5-43b7-8d1c-3d3a166d431b"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 8 = ?",
              "answer": 80,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "013a7858-a114-432c-8c2b-f8f5325d7563"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 9 = ?",
              "answer": 90,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "4befdc87-6dd6-43b1-a09b-636fc8e022fd"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 10 = ?",
              "answer": 100,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "4e628992-ccad-4001-a9dc-0225b57258dd"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 11 = ?",
              "answer": 110,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "fb71d11f-7216-4436-b29a-fb930e833c36"
          },
          {
              "question": "10 x 12 = ?",
              "answer": 120,
              "needsPractice": false,
              "id": "134b16c2-246a-49fe-8e49-80bbb5fe0122"
          }
      ],
      "id": "bd35ffff-350a-46ca-b4f0-ebdb14f44882"
  }
]
